<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>eric hambro</title>
    <link>https://erichambro.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on eric hambro</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 10:58:08 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://erichambro.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>automatic documentation of python functions</title>
      <link>https://erichambro.com/projects/thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erichambro.com/projects/thesis/</guid>
      <description> For my Master&amp;rsquo;s thesis at UCL, I investigated how the latest NLP techniques could be applied to written source code, to generate English description of source code arguments. The submitted thesis can be downloaded here and source code is available below. It got the second highest mark in the year.
Write Up Coming Soon The Stack  python3.6 tensorflow numpy sphinx matplotlib LaTeX  Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rowlang</title>
      <link>https://erichambro.com/projects/rowlang/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jun 2018 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erichambro.com/projects/rowlang/</guid>
      <description> [In Progress]
Write Up Coming Soon The Stack  python3.5 tensorflow numpy  Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>monty</title>
      <link>https://erichambro.com/projects/monty/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erichambro.com/projects/monty/</guid>
      <description> Monty is a repository of bots that work with the smithers poker bot engine. Currently these bots are quite naive, but the aim is to investigate multi-agent RL in this scenario.
You can watch a very naive game between bots (prerecorded and slowed down to human-viewing speed) here.
Write Up Coming Soon The Stack  python3.5 pyzmq numpy  Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>smithers</title>
      <link>https://erichambro.com/projects/smithers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Apr 2017 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erichambro.com/projects/smithers/</guid>
      <description>Smithers is a poker bot server in C++. It allows your bots to play poker against each other very fast over a network. It is implemented in C++, partly as an exercise, partly as a learning opportunity in learning a low level stack, and partly because it&amp;rsquo;s fast.
In terms of its structure, Smithers is composed of a configuration for a mongrel2 server (which hooks up the http/websockets requests to ZeroMQ endpoints) and an executable which communicates with those endpoints and effectively runs the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>twirps</title>
      <link>https://erichambro.com/projects/twirps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erichambro.com/projects/twirps/</guid>
      <description> Twirps is a project to collect, analyse and visualise politician&amp;rsquo;s tweets. A preliminary version was built in the run up to the 2015 UK General Election, and it was later turned into a Flask web app in 2017, using a graph Neo4j database as it&amp;rsquo;s datastore.
Write Up Coming Soon The Stack  python2.7 Flask (webapp) Neo4j (backend) d3.js (visualisation) tweepy (interact with twitter) Heroku (deployment)  Github </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>snayk</title>
      <link>https://erichambro.com/projects/snayk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2015 10:58:08 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://erichambro.com/projects/snayk/</guid>
      <description>snayk is a game in 400 lines of pure javascript, written during my time at the Recurse Center. It is simply the classic game of snake, adapted to use polar coordinates, instead of Cartesian ones. You can play snayk here.
Background I had just finished my physics degree at Cambridge, and had already spent some time thinking about how different coordinate systems can make problems easier or harder.
While at RC, I attended a seminar run by Mary Rose Cook in game development, in which she laid out the basics of coding up Space Invaders, based on her very popular annotated code blog posts.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>